[HANNAH] Yes.
I am the chairman's daughter.
But I have no interest
in seeing him.
Hannah. Don't go, Hannah.
Hannah.
Chairman Song already
knows about everything.
He's going to be here soon.
He left my mother and me.
I don't need him!
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
He's a good man,
and he wants to
be part of your life.
He already missed his chance.
It's far too late now.
It's too late!
I know you're angry.
I get that.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
My mother...
gambled everything away,
including me.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
And she sold me
to my own father.
There's a difference here,
Hannah.
Your father...
wants to make things right.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tell me.
You tell me.
If your mother came back,
would you give her
a second chance?
[MUSIC BECOMES TENSE]
Do you understand me?
You get me, right?
[HANNAH BREATHES DEEPLY]
Please don't force me
to meet the person
who hurt me
if you can't even face
your own ghost.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]